ANGELA LEE





Taipei, Taiwan angela.tylee25@gmail.com



in www.linkedin.com/in/angela-tylee

ABOUT ME

I'm a frontend developer specializing in React and Bootstrap, passionate about building functional and user-friendly websites. With a background in customer service and project management, I bring strong cross-team communication skills and focus on solutions that prioritize user experience.

EXPERTISE / SKILLS

• Frontend Development: React.js Bootstrap Git, CRA, Vite Responsive Design HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES6+)

Soft Skill: Problem-Solving User-Centric Thinking Cross-Team Collaboration

EDUCATION

National Chiao Tung University

2014 - 2019

Bachelor of English Literature, Minor in Management Science

LANGUAGE

- English (TOFEL100 / TOEIC950)
- Mandarin (Native)

PROJECTS

Portfolio

https://angela-tylee.github.io/portfolio/

Furniture E-commerce Website

https://angela-tylee.github.io/carpento/

WORK EXPERIENCE

CuboAi

Dec, 2019 - Jun. 2023

Customer Success Team Lead

- As the team expanded 5x and 3 major product released, led initiatives of 5 projects that scaffold or optimize flow, including comprehensive Training Program, Internal Knowledge Base, and re-structure Customer Help Center.
- Architected 60 key operational workflows and released the first comprehensive SOPs, ensuring process standardization and service quality.
- Assisted with shifting the operation center to the Philippines team by cultivating 1 shift leader and 1 subject matter expert.
- Developed agent self-help tools for warranty, shipping, and subscription calculations, improving service accuracy, and reducing operation error rate.

Customer Success Specialist

- Achieved a 96% first-level resolution rate (team average of 80%), the highest in the team, while maintaining a CSAT above 90%, proven strong logical problem-solving and root cause analysis skills.
- Maintained a library of 629 troubleshooting templates, built 447 response templates, and clear logical troubleshooting steps designed to improve response accuracy and speed.
- Delivered structured product knowledge and operation flow training for the Philippines support team.

Mithril Technology

Nov. 2018 - Aug. 2019

Customer Success Intern

 Monitored global investor's community, analyzed investor discussions, and identified key concerns, enabling proactive responses that improved engagement and trust among global investors.